making this third and short gives them better options on
offense.
Aluminor may have moved early but there's no yellow.
Here comes dart.
There goes the flag.
There goes the throw.
Bellinger the tight ends got it.
The yardage good for a first down hit by Jones.
Look at nine guys,
eight guys right at the line of scrimmage.
How do you decipher who to block?
Battle down.
Incomplete.
Pressure was there.
Fourth and seven.
Here comes the punting unit.
This is the game defense of Lyman.
Sure enough that's been the story so far.
It's a sweep
and it goes to Marvin Mims.
We're playing better on defense.
We're getting pressure.
Our special teams is better.
It's an overall team effort.
Third and 11. Nick's going long.
The catch made but maybe shy of the first down.
Grabbed on the play by Sutton.
They're
running 53% of the time which is number
one in the NFL the last three weeks.
They had
72 against the Eagles last game.
Here is a second and 10. The
dancing dart chased by Benito.
Throws and it's caught.
Robinson.
What a grab.
Sneers it out of the air.
46 yard line.
Terrific.
Catch Tracy the back.
Good cup.
Now here he goes winding out
the line.
He's got him.
Touchdown.
Holy smokes.
He was wide open.
44 yard touchdown strike.
And the Giants are on the board first in Denver.
Watch he's going to release up the field here
and he gets lost.
He goes to the outside like he's
going to block and then they lose him.
Excellent job by Dart keeping his eyes upfield.
In the pistol formation.
Second down and six.
It is Mims.
Down the sideline he goes.
Shove that about by Newman.
Back in motion.
Harvey gets the call.
He gets the first down carving his way into that defense.
This drive began back at the six.
Hit by Burns.
What down on the play.
Defensive coordinator in this unit
ranked number 28 in the NFL coming in.
Third down 18. They need the 42. Bolts the block.
Going deep and on the side and incomplete.
Looking for Franklin.
Flott was right there.
It's incomplete.
It's fourth and 18.
Down and 10. Here they come hard.
There he goes outside.
Scataboo crashing his way into Singleton.
Takes a couple to bring him down and finally hit by Roach.
Thomas the block.
Jackson Dart to the yard.
He's got Pellinger again.
He can't get by
a fun go but he does get the first down deep in Planko territory.
Man hurts in motion.
First and 10. Dart.
Here comes the pressure from Cooper and down he goes.
Sack back at
the 15. Dart.
Thomas the block.
Off to the running back.
Scataboo.
There was a block inside.
He's going to stiffen his way in.
Touchdown chance.
Scataboo.
Because of that patience allowing the block to happen,
Reed getting outside.
Extra point here is no good.
Megatonne with the miss.
To the air.
Blocked by Dobbins.
And underneath they go.
It's caught here by Atkins from behind.
Grabs them.
And they get a first down.
Catch and run.
Near midfield.
Fourth and three.
High snap.
Nicks will take it.
He's going to get the first.
Hits the deck.
Down he goes.
Right in front of Belton.
They know what kind of waters they're swimming in here.
Third down and eight.
Nicks the second year back.
He's being chased in the play by Alexander and throws.
Sutton at the 10. Inside the five and Flott will bring him down.
72 is their left tackle Garrett Bowles.
They move Pelczewski to the tackle.
Yes and there's the throw deflected for Bowles and incomplete.
He's your big target down here.
You called it.
There's Sutton.
Oh, killed.
What a big time hit.
Belton.
Belts him.
Scataboo the bat.
Breathing space at the 17. First and 10.
Dardell taking himself and he's got room to
roam and drilled right there and hit by Jones.
Tumbles ahead.
Here comes Robinson in motion who
they like to look for on third down.
They bring four hit as he throws.
Incomplete.
Setting up here back at the 20 with
the second and 14 and they need the
34 for the first.
Miners of block.
There they come and got him.
Back at the 14 yard line.
Brian Burns his second sack today.
Nine for the season.
He goes.
Onyx nine and 19. Second down and seven.
Bowles the left tackle block and he'll find his receiver
and that is Sutton over there working on a debo.
Gain of seven in the first series after the half.
Good time.
McClintchia block.
Downfield.
Oh and he had the receiver a little bit.
There was Franklin.
After the Bronco pun at the 15. It's a pitch
out to Scataboo who gets away from one.
Looked like he was devoured early there.
With a big time hit by John Franklin Myers who blew it up.
Third down and four.
Dark to the air.
Illuminora block.
Dard will find his receiver.
It's caught here.
Theo Johnson as he gallops to the 40
yard line and upended on the play.
Third down and 12. They need midfield.
Dard.
Thomas a block.
Robinson looking for a block
and he bumps into Schloman and he takes
it outside and he's got the first down.
A catch and run and a late flag thrown.
Second down nine.
Giants tight ends.
Big today.
Five catches 113 yards.
Dard to the air.
Good cup.
Illuminora held him off.
Tillman will chase and they got him.
Second sack today.
Second field goal earlier this season.
Third down 18. Ty Weckert's coming in.
Dard deflected again and once again a talent.
His second deflected pass today of a giant quarterback throw.
Down for third down today.
Two of nine.
Here they are third and 11. Bowles the block.
Incomplete.
Ingram with the coverage by Muehisao.
Dard under center.
12,
11 of 23. And two touchdowns and Scataboo with the Bellinger block.
Cuts it outside.
Hofanga has a beat on him but look at him.
Swirl is way outside and get another couple yards.
There have been no turnovers against the Eagles.
Ten days ago.
No turnovers today.
Robinson second 11.
Trying to get a block from Humphrey and moves down close to a
first down with McMillan making the stop a catch and run of ten.
Kevin there five of 11 on third down coming into this Denver's
defense is number one in the NFL on third down defense.
Tracy a big hole.
Galloping.
Touchdown.
Touchdown Giants.
A burst of 31 yards.
A stunning display and the Giants have gone up now by a count of
19 to nothing.
There's no one there as he comes up to the line
of scrims.
Watch everything collapses.
Hofanga goes out to
the flat.
You see that Thomas block.
He sealed him inside.
He sealed it inside.
Scataboo in.
And Dard will get it from
Sloan and it was caught by Robinson but held out with a
good hit by Brandon Jones.
Those are living up to what they've
done previously.
That's the second most penalized team in
terms of yards.
J.K.
Dobbins cutting inside.
Newman couldn't
get him and hit deep in the secondary.
Lawrence is right
over Wattenberg.
He must be feeling that pressure, right?
Because we've seen a couple of those today first and ten going
deep and caught.
Nice grab made.
Sutton Banks is over there
covering.
With Dobbins.
Prentice with the block.
Dobbins with a
hole.
Got a block in there from Boczeski.
Got a block in there
from Cropman.
Takes it inside the 20 and near the 16 yard line.
32 yard run by J.K.
Dobbins.
Right there first and ten Denver.
Look they catch the Giants in an overload to this side.
So what do you do?
Go this way.
There's only two defenders out there.
You've got bodies.
You can take away anything they have
with that over shift to the strong side.
Get a
weak side run which is exactly.
Dobbins a block to the end zone deflected and did Franklin get it
on the ricochet.
Touchdown Denver.
On the deflected ball.
Defensive play knocking it away from Sutton right at the goal
line.
He's going to 14. The ball's batted up in the air.
Great job by Franklin extending and staying alive.
Staying with
the play.
Able to get it.
See the knee down.
Secures the ball.
Cordell Flott was defending Sutton and had the deflection.
And unfortunately.
It ricocheted.
Nicks for two.
Clap Sutton.
In front of Belton.
And two more on the board.
19-8 is the score.
Dard is 12-24 for 2-10 through the air and two touchdowns.
They bring the blitz.
Darn it.
Across the middle it's caught.
Robinson on the move.
Caught down from behind by McMillan.
More breathing space.
48 yard line trying to answer that Denver touchdown pass moments ago.
First intense, Gattaboo busting free.
And here he goes into the secondary.
Ram rotting his way down inside the 35.
Notre Dame running back from Appleton,
Wisconsin.
Rocky Blyers second down nine.
Tracer to the back.
Bellinger on the move.
They pull him.
And it's red well and here comes the entourage.
Scattered to the back.
Third and 17. Caught on the ricochet.
It's crapped here by the Gallup and Johnson.
He'll be chased to the plate by Barron.
Did he get in?
He did touchdown.
Johnson.
Well,
just like we saw a second ago when Franklin got
the ricochet off of the Sutton at the goal line and he was able
to finish the play,
Johnson never gives up on the play.
And it's third down and five.
Bade was the back and he gets the
call.
He's looking for a block.
Pucheski gives it to him and he
takes it for a first down catch and run.
Giants without two
starters in their secondary underneath.
It's Ingram.
He's
got to get to the 41 and a big hit right there by Andrew Phillips.
Knocking out a former giant Ingram on the catch and run the
31 year old tight anchor.
Not get it picked up nine.
Another
first down on this drive for Denver.
Nicks again.
Bulls trying to hold him off.
Nicks will be on
the run.
He's got the first down.
And Okereke will make sure
he stays to the boundary.
But here the Giants have had control.
Second down and ten.
Dumping
it off Bade.
Got a block out there from Miners and the center Wattenberg.
And then brought
down as he wheels his way down to the seven.
Picks up 12. It's first and goal for Denver.
And down and goal.
Fake handoff.
Here comes Nicks.
Pursue Thibodeau getting a block.
And
he'll get inside the pylon.
That is a touchdown.
Ready.
Nicks
with the block by Bade
to the end zone.
Caught for two.
And crab by Franklin.
Denver's not stacked in at the
line of scrimmage.
It's a third and five.
They come up the middle.
Heavy pressure in
the middle.
And it's picked up by Sternad.
He breaks the tackle.
Breaks another.
Now inside the 20. Oh, disaster.
What a play.
Sternad's going to be lined up in the weak side.
And he's going to work his way out over here.
This is right where he came from last time where he
blitzed the A gap and was able to get the pressure.
Dard not able to get anything on that.
Watch his feet.
So he can't step into it.
He's stepping over a defender.
Sternad is able to get in the lane.
And because he can't get enough elevation on that pass.
Timely interception.
The first big mistake for Dard.
A turnover on downs.
End of the first half.
Last two.
Two touchdowns.
Here's a second ten.
Nicks crumb the block.
Underneath they go.
Franklin.
And then he was crab by O'Kara K and Moussel.
And he's down to the 14 yard line.
Harvey the
back.
Nicks chased by Tibbito.
Backpedaling touchdown.
Harvey.
And the Broncos are back
in business.
And cash in on the interception of Dard.
Getting to the flat.
Here he is right here.
But watch the defender as he's trying to get
through.
His own guy causes him to cut underneath.
Watch.
It
slows him down just enough.
That he can't get out there in time.
Dard on third down and eight.
Boy they're crowding that line.
Here they come.
They bring five.
Dard to the air.
No! To Robinson.
McMillan the coverage.
Fourth down and eight.
Nicks to the air.
Bowls with the block.
Nicks going long.
And caught by Mims.
First down.
Giants have won the entire game.
Nicks underneath.
Engrum out of bounds.
Oh he stayed in.
And
finally blocked down by Belton.
It's a catch and run.
He's inside the 20. Running back will
be Badang.
Nicks will take it himself on first and 10. Blocked
by Bowls.
Touchdown Denver.
The Broncos have their first lead
today.
Come back to take a 30-26 lead over the New York Giants.
So Sutton's going to come down and crack Tibbito.
Bowls gets
out in space.
He's able to get up and then he seals it.
And
McGlinchey with the block.
McGlinchey gets a block down low too.
And Bow Nicks with the
touchdown run.
His second of the season.
18 yards.
It's first and 10. Thomas the block.
Crumbling pocket.
Grab below.
Zach Allen got him.
Second out in 14. Tracy remains.
Dard.
Good cup.
Going deep.
Oh he's got him.
And he missed him.
Looking for Chaelin Hyatt.
Jackson Dard third down in 19. Moving up
as time downfield and broken up by Sertan.
Looking for Robinson fourth in 19. Dard.
Barely get it.
Here they come.
Here he goes.
And it is
bobbled and caught.
Robinson reels it in.
But he's got it.
I think he did.
McMillan was right there.
And they get the
first down.
Dard.
Barely get it.
Here they come.
Here he goes.
And it is bobbled and caught.
Robinson reels it in.
But he's
got it.
He did.
McMillan was right there.
And they get the
first down.
This is his start.
Steps up in the pocket.
He hits
Robinson but right there.
Franklin Meyers with the hit that
gets the extra 15. Now it's down to the 40. And again plenty of
time in the clock.
101. And is that Payton all the way out with
the officials?
He's down at the two yard line out on the field.
He's got to be careful not to get a flat.
He just got a flat.
He just got a flag.
I think what his argument
is that the receiver grabbed Moss.
But Moss
wasn't turning around for the ball as the ball was coming in.
There's Payton all the
way down there.
He's down the two yard line trying to
get in the middle of the officials.
That's what draws the extra flag.
Two fouls in the play both by the defense.
Pass interference.
21. Right rule.
The ball is placed in the star of the foul.
Automatic.
First down.
It was also unsportsmanlike conduct on the head coach.
First and goal.
Dirk will run it himself and dives.
And short.
Short inside the one.
Let's see.
He catches.
I don't know.
I don't think his knee ever went down.
So New York
calls the timeout.
They can't challenge it.
His contact.
That looks like a touchdown.
It looks like a touchdown.
It's right.
Watch right here.
He never touches the ground.
His
forearm until the thigh comes down.
The ball is in the end
of the line.
The knee never goes down.
Right there he makes
contact.
But the ball is already in.
Balls well over the goal
line.
He missed earlier.
And oh no! He missed that one again.
First and 10 from their
23. And no timeouts.
Nix. Long down the middle and caught at the
48 yard line and grabbed by Mims.
What a catch by Mims and a
thicket of defenders.
Wow. It's a first and five.
Nix. And caught
by Sutton.
Got it on the side.
Newbin was there.
Croshaw the
rookie will hold it.
Will once.
39 yard field goal for the win.
He got it! Denver's won!
So improbable.
NFL teams had won 1,602 consecutive games when leading by 18-1.